# 



ACCOUNTANT - DATA ANALYST

 $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar$ 

**\*\***\*\*

 $\star\star\star\star$ 

 $\bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar \bigstar$ 

 $\star\star\star\star$ 

 $\star\star\star\star\star$ 

 $\star\star\star\star$ 

 $\star\star\star\star$ 

 $\star\star\star\star$ 

\*\*\*

\*\*\*

\*\*\*

# Some Skills

Python

SQL

Power Query

Microsoft Excel

Javascript

HTML

CSS

Microsoft Access

Looker

Power BI

Visual basic

Google

Appscripts

I have more than nine years of experience in the retail sector, focused on internal auditing and payment method processing.

My goal is to automate processes and use advanced technologies to generate valuable information. Currently, I am interested in developing my skills in programming and big data management to meet the needs of my clients and offer a more complete service.

## Contact



+54 9 291 577-4569



Bahía Blanca, Argentina.



martin.batarev@gmail.com



/martin-batarev

# Experience

### Supervised professional practice

El mundo de la parrilla

August 2013 to September 2013

 Computer development of internal reports Purchases, Debts, Cash Flows, Results and Cost Study (Reports).

#### Senior Internal Auditor

Cooperativa Obrera Ltda.

April 2014 to September 2019

- Internal process audit of the organization covering areas such as logistics, purchasing, points of sales, administration, inventory and humans resources.
- Definition of control processes in the development of new systems used in the organization.
- Annual audit of financial statements in collaboration with the External Auditor.

## Administrative Manager of Payment Methods

Cooperativa Obrera Ltda.

October 2019 to June 2023

- Administrative control of payment methods.
- · Development of reports and management dashboards.
- Implementation of new payment methods.
- 11 people in charge

#### **ACADEMIC TRAINING**

- College of the Sacred Heart of Jesus Graduated in 2007
- March 2008 to December 2013 National University of the South - Accountant

#### **ACADEMIC TRAINING**

- Introduction to programming with Python | June 2020
- Introduction to machine learning | June 2020
- Pandas Library | May 2021
- Intermediate Machine Learning | July 2020
- Data Visualization | July 2020
- Introduction to SQL | January 2022

## Languages

- Native Spanish
- English (intermediate/advanced) First Certificate

Visit My Web
Portfolio

SCAN ME

